Jovi Julian Hendri

Jl. Moh. Toha Gg. Sura No. 64/203D, Bandung City, West Java, Indonesia 081313162548

jovijulian2002@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jovijulian2002/

https://jovijulian.github.io/

I am last year college student at Institut Digital Ekonomi LPKIA Bandung, majoring in Computer Science with a concentration in Information Technology. As a Computer Science major, I have interest in web development and backend development. I have expertise in programming languages such as PHP, JavaScript, Golang, as well as Laravel Frameworks and ExpressJS.

Experiences

Full Stack Developer • QUEM Creative Studio

Maret 2024 - Mei 2024 | Bandung, Indonesia

- Manage microservice enimalbiz applications
- Carrying out further development of the enimalbiz application for certain features
- Adjustment for the front end of the web application using VueJs
- Create REST API for front-end web and mobile

Assistant Lecturer • Institut Digital Ekonomi LPKIA

Oktober 2023 - Januari 2024 | Bandung, Indonesia

• Help lectures on pratical subjects (Web Programming 3 - Web Service)

Product Manager • AntriQue

September 2023 - Desember 2023 | Bandung, Indonesia

- Create a Project Plan such as Create a project document in Notion that includes the project's objectives, scope, timeline, budget, and stakeholders, Identify and allocate the resources required for the project, including team members, equipment, and budget.
- Carrying out task management such as creating a Trello work board containing a list of tasks, status and assignments for team members, monitoring the progress of tasks, updating status and resolving problems that arise, managing assignments and priorities by utilizing Trello features such as labels, deadlines, and checklists.
- Performing Reporting and Evaluation such as Generating periodic project progress reports using Notion, which includes performance statistics, comparisons to initial goals, and qualitative analysis, conducting post-project evaluations to identify lessons learned and improvements that can be implemented in the future.

Back End Developer • QUEM Creative Studio

Agustus 2023 - Desember 2023 | Bandung, Indonesia

- Create a database design according to the needs that will be implemented in the application
- Create REST API for Web and Mobile Front-end
- Manage tasks for the web developer team such as determining targets, conveying feedback from PM / Analyst
- Reporting and evaluating work that has been done to PM / Analyst

Back End Developer • Rumah Sakit Ratumas Binjai

- Upgraded and refactored the bridging system from version 1 to version 2.
- Implemented BPJS Pusat standards in the SIMRS application.
- Ensured connectivity between the SIMRS application of Rumah Sakit Ratumas Binjai and the BPJS Pusat application.
- Enhanced integration for managing patients under the BPJS category.
- Conducted testing and validation of the system after the version upgrade.

Back End Developer • Rumah Sakit Graha Bunda Aceh

April 2023 - Mei 2023 | Bandung, Indonesia

- Upgraded and refactored the bridging system from version 1 to version 2.
- Implemented BPJS Pusat standards in the SIMRS application.
- Ensured connectivity between the SIMRS application of Rumah Sakit Graha Bunda Aceh and the BPJS Pusat application.
- Enhanced integration for managing patients under the BPJS category.
- Conducted testing and validation of the system after the version upgrade.

Frontend Web Developer • AntriQue

Juli 2022 - Maret 2023 | Bandung, Indonesia

- Participate build Project Helpdesk Pospay as Fullstack using Laravel.
- Participate developing AntriQue Ads as Frontend using Laravel and Vue.
- Build TV Layout for BRI Client as Frontend using PHP and JavaScript.
- Build Tutorial Page for Merchant AntriQue as Frontend using Vue.
- Participate developing AntriQue App.
- Become Volunteer in Company Event.
- Become scrum moderator every week.

Assistant Lecturer • Institut Digital Ekonomi LPKIA

Oktober 2021 - Juli 2022 | Bandung, Indonesia

• Help lectures on pratical subjects (Business Application Computers 1 & 2)

Programmer • PT. Amal Solution

Agustus 2020 - November 2020 | Bandung, Indonesia

- Participate in making company project programs
- Doing learning about node js, Maria DB, Neo 4J

Programmer • Sagara Technology

Agustus 2019 - Oktober 2019 | Bandung, Indonesia

- Participate in the creation of job vacancies menu on the company website
- Make articles for company websites every 1 week per month

Education

Institut Digital Ekonomi LPKIA

Computer Science • 2020 - 2024

There are many related courses to support my hard & soft skills, such as Algoritma dan Pemrograman, Basis Data 1-3, Pemrograman Web 1-3, Pemrograman Piranti, Manajemen Proyek, Analisis Sistem Informasi, Komputer Aplikasi Bisnis 1-2, Human Relations, Professional Development and many more

Activities and societies:

- Help lectures on pratical subjects (Web Programming 3) as Assistant Lecturer October 2021 July 2022
- Help lectures on pratical subjects (Business Application Computers 1 & 2) as Assistant Lecturer October 2021 July 2022
- Became the internal division coordinator for the faculty organization, HIMAKOM / HIMATIK 2021 20
- Became the IT Coodinator for the extracurricular major, LOOP 2021 2022

SMK MEDIKACOM Bandung

Computer Software Engineering • 2017 - 2020

Learning about programming for 3 years, learn about HTML, PHP native, Java, Android native, DBMS, Codelgniter

Activities and societies: Member of a programming club off our high school, Alogical Backend

Skills

- REST API
- Laravel Framework
- NodeJS
- Express.js
- PHP
- JavaScript
- VueJS
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- GIT
- GCP Compute Engine
- Microsoft Office

Language

- Indonesian Fluent
- English Intermediate

Powered by CakeResume